var questionBank = [

	{
		question: 'Who played lead guitar for the British rock band Queen?',
		answers: ['Jimmy Page', 'Brian May', 'Jeff Beck', 'Eric Clapton'],
		correct: 'Brian May'
	},

	{
		question: 'In music, the space between one musical pitch and another with double its frequency is called what?',
		answers: ['Unison', 'Chord', 'Octave', 'Double'],
		correct: 'Octave'
	},

	{
		question: 'Which of the Beatles is barefoot on the Abby Road album cover?',	
		answers: ['John Lennon', 'Ringo Starr', 'Paul McCartney', 'George Harrison'],
		correct: 'Paul McCartney'
	},

	{
		question: 'What American singer-songwriter wrote and first recorded the song "Blue Suede Shoes" in 1955?',	
		answers: ['Buddy Holly', 'Carl Perkins', 'Elvis Presley', 'Roy Orbison'],
		correct: 'Carl Perkins'
	},

	{
		question: 'What song by Michael Jackson contains the lyrics "Annie are you OK?"',	
		answers: ['Thriller', 'Bad', 'Smooth Criminal', 'Black or White'],
		correct: 'Smooth Criminal'
	},

	{
		question: 'In what city was Ludwig van Beethoven born?',	
		answers: ['Bonn', 'Berlin', 'Hamburg', 'Frankfurt'],
		correct: 'Bonn'
	},

	{
		question: 'Where was the very first Hard Rock Cafe opened?',	
		answers: ['Los Angeles', 'Madrid', 'Amsterdam', 'London'],
		correct: 'London'
	},

	{
		question: 'How many keys are on most baby grand pianos?',	
		answers: ['100', '99', '88', '77'],
		correct: '88'
	},

	{
		question: 'Which pop star sang the national anthem at the 50th Super Bowl?',	
		answers: ['Madonna', 'Katy Perry', 'Beyonc√©', 'Lady Gaga'],
		correct: 'Lady Gaga'
	},

	{
		question: 'ABBA was a pop group from what country?',	
		answers: ['Norway', 'Sweden', 'Finland', 'Belgium'],
		correct: 'Sweden'
	},

	{
		question: 'Which rock music group has received the most Grammy Awards?',	
		answers: ['The Rolling Stones', 'Nirvana', 'U2', 'AC/DC'],
		correct: 'U2'
	}
];